(waves crashing)
(birds chirping)
(dramatic music)
(Sam gasps)
(heart beating)
(Sam panting)
- Hey.
Virginia?
Hey.
Virginia.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
Help.
(tense music)
(Sam panting)
Jesus.
- Tonight you will be
part of big stage history
as we welcome back the
king of comedy himself,
Dom Fletcher.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat drum music)
(MC speaks indistinctly)
- [Dom] "Per your contract,
you are required...
Ha.
...to perform tonight."
I won't.
I won't come on stage.
- [Crew Member] Mr. Fletcher.
Mr. Fletcher, you're on.
- [Dom] I'm not.
- [Crew Member] Mr.
Fletcher, hello?
(door knocks)
- [Dom] They want a performance,
I'll give them a performance.
- [MC] There is Dom Fletcher.
- [Dom] Thank you.
Thank you, no, thank you.
And now for my final act.
(gun clicks)
(gun fires)
(gun clatters)
(body thuds)
(crowd screams)
(dramatic music)
- If you loved our last
performer, Layne Brown,
you're in for a treat.
A homegrown talent, a Reno
boy through and through,
please put your hands
together for Sam Reinhold.
(audience applauds)
- Hey, hey, hey.
Hi everybody, Sam Reinhold.
And in honor of the
late great Dom Fletcher,
I brought to the stage
a little friend of mine,
his name is Eugene.
Why, hello y'all, I'm Eugene.
Eugene and I are gonna do a
little performance for you.
I'm gonna start with
some impersonations.
Back in the day, Marlon Brando,
before he became Marlon Brando,
tried out to be Yogi Bear.
Remember the cartoon?
This is how that
audition sounded.
Hey, boo-boo.
Hey boo-boo, let's go
steal some picnic baskets.
Listen, Mr. Ranger, I'm
not your average bear.
Boo-boo.
- [Audience Member]
Keep your day job.
- Okay.
Now, for a little Sean Connery.
There's only five things I like
better than sex in the evening.
Sex in the morning,
sex after breakfast,
sex during lunch, sex before
dinner, and sex during sex.
The name is Bond, James Bond.
Hello, Miss Moneypenny.
(wall knocks)
(painting clatters)
- [Mrs. Winslow]
Your Connery blows.
- Thanks, Mrs. Winslow.
(phone vibrates)
Ah, look at that, you
got a new follower, Sam.
129 followers.
Good for you, fellow,
good, good for you.
How does Layne Brown have 8,000
followers and you have 129?
- Sammy, coffee.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
- [Telemarketer] Mr.
Reinhold, do you-
- Hey, I told you to take
our name off your list.
Please.
Hey, Sammy, have a super
duper day at work today.
- Oh, I'm running late.
- Hey, your Connery
is sounding amazing.
Do not listen to Mrs. Winslow.
- I loves you, Gramps.
- Loves you, boy.
- [Sam] Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye-bye-bye.
(door thuds)
(tense music)
(goat bleats)
- [Shop Announcer]
Manager in aisle 10.
Mr. Van Sickle.
(tense music)
- [Connie] Ah... Yeah, we
only take real money here.
- Well, that's not
what that says.
(tense music)
- Can I get security on
register three, please.
- [Walter] Security?
Really?
- Seriously, Connie?
Hi.
Yeah, we'll get all this
sorted out, don't worry.
- You are the rock against
which the darkness breaks.
You are the rock against
You are the rock,
hey, Mr. Van Sickle.
- What in the Sam
Hill are you doing?
For the better
part of four years,
you have wasted my time
with your half-ass theatrics
and your crappy impersonations.
You talk to yourself
like an idiot.
You're a slacker.
You waste my time.
When you waste my time,
you waste your time
'cause your time is my time.
Here's your mop.
Oh, and one last thing, okay?
Women's bathroom, it's like
a murder scene in there.
Have a super duper day.
- Well, that is some
wild and crazy stuff, Ed.
That is some wild
and crazy stuff.
I am the great Zambini.
- Ha-ha-ha, you
are correct, Sir.
(Sam laughs)
- Well, thank you. Ed.
- Why do you only seem real
when you're doing
someone else's voice?
- I don't know.
I guess I have nothing to say.
- You should have had something
you say to Van Sickle today,
I know that much.
- [Sam] You saw that, huh?
- Yep.
The guy's such a bully.
You're getting better.
- At what?
- Your voices.
- Thanks.
[TV Host] Our next guest has
been entertaining audiences
from Japan to Russia to-
- All right, Grandpa, I'll
see you in the morning.
- Hey, Sammy, where
are you going?
You always used to love to
watch this show with me.
- I'm gonna go perform,
I'm going to the club.
- Sammy, there are
two things I remember
about my life vividly.
My fishing trips with you.
- Yeah, quicksand.
- I saved your life.
- But I lost the boots.
- There's a cost to everything.
(Sam laughs)
Okay, fishing
and us watching
this show together.
Come on, we never
missed an episode.
- All right.
I was gonna leave
a little early but-
- Yeah, no.
- I'll stay for a minute.
- Don't forget, Sam,
it was always your
dream to be right here
on The Latest Show.
- Yeah, it still is.
- And you're gonna make it.
- [Dom] Owen?
Owen, how you doing?
- [Owen] I'm doing fine.
So happy to be here, Jack.
- Was he some kind of big deal?
- This guy?
- Yeah, this guy.
- That's Dom Fletcher,
this guy's a legend.
- He's been good to me.
- [Grandpa] Well,
they were playing
his last episode
'cause you know,
the gruesome death.
- [Sam] He was an original,
he was quite unique.
- Marlon Brando was
the last original actor
to come outta Hollywood.
And everybody else is
just imitating him.
You know, naturalism
and activism and-
- Naturalism and activism.
- I've been dying to
ask you all these years.
- Yes, well go for
it, it's your job.
Yes, yeah, yeah, it's part
of the job description.
- No kidding, it's his job, Dom.
What are you, choking on
your own tongue out here?
You're on television.
(audience laughing)
- He doesn't mince
words, doesn't he?
- No, he does not, no, no.
You had a question?
- Yeah, yeah, well, I
hate to say it, Dom,
but you know when you
first started out-
- That's rude, I'm sorry.
(audience laughing)
- You weren't exactly,
how should I put this?
Refined.
- I wasn't good,
Jack, you can say it.
I was crap.
- Crap?
You sucked, Dom.
(audience laughing)
- I don't know if I would've
put it that way exactly,
but there is some truth to that.
- I'm being ganged up on here.
Yes, but you're both
right, yes, yes.
- Flash-forward a few years,
and then all of a sudden, bam,
you're now a ventriloquist
out of nowhere
and you're on top of the world.
- [Dom] Yeah.
- [Jack] Explain this to me.
- Ventriloquism?
(audience laughs)
- No, I know what you mean.
Representation, Jack, just
got some good representation.
- [Jack] Wow.
Could you give my
number to your agent?
I would like him to
represent me please.
- No, I mean, you're
doing just fine.
(audience laughing)
(Dom speaks faintly)
- All right, I
gotta go, Grandpa.
I'll see you in the morning.
- [Grandpa] Break a leg.
And remember-
- I loves you.
- I loves you, Gramps.
- Uh, it's ah, it's.. Hey, you
know, I think it's about time
to cut the commercial, isn't it?
- You drunk.
- I don't know if you
guys have noticed,
Patrick Mahomes sounds a
lot like Kermit the Frog.
Hey-o, it's me, Patrick Mahomes.
Hey.
Jason Momoa and Macho
Man Randy Savage.
Oh yeah.
And weirdly enough,
they sound exactly
like the Kool-Aid man.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, they really
think you suck, Sam.
Of course, then there's
Christian Slater
and Jack Nicholson.
Listen, you sound like
me, you look like me,
you're even doing
the eyebrow thing
and it's freaking me out.
Here's Johnny.
That's my line.
- Getting better
every time, Sam.
Nobody kills at Shims.
- Yeah, it just
feels like dying.
- You gotta be
used to it by now.
- Ah.
- Look at this.
- What?
- Gray skies are clearing
up, put on that happy face.
- What's this?
- You got some fan
mail, that's a first.
(tense music)
- "We represent the
world's top musicians,
actors, comedians, news
anchors, and leader.
We would like to represent you.
Simply sign this invitation
and we will be in touch."
(tense music)
- [Dad] Do I love you this much?
No.
Do I love you this much?
I love you this much.
Nobody loves you
more than Daddy.
Happy birthday, my Gin Bug.
- Well, hey, hey, hey, friend.
Oh, what's wrong?
You look sad.
Are you okay?
- Today is the anniversary
of my dad's death,
and I just wish I could
talk to him, that's all.
- Oh.
I'm sorry.
- Why do you have so much
pep in your step today?
(Sam laughs)
You get into the no-doz again?
- Nope, nope.
Last night I was at the
club, and guess what?
- Hmm?
- I got an invitation
from an agency.
They wanna represent me.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- What's the agency?
- I don't know.
But they have huge stars.
Apparently they
represent huge stars
and they want to represent me.
- That's great, Sam.
- Yeah.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- What did the invitation say?
- Well, it said that
I had to sign it.
- [Virginia] Was anybody
with the invitation or?
- No.
- Did you sign it?
(tense music)
- Yeah.
Is it weird?
Yeah.
You know what?
It was probably MC Tony.
He's always pranking me
and doing stuff like that.
He was probably just
trying to tease me.
- I get it.
You wish someone would just
waltz in and wave a magic wand,
catapult your career, make
everything perfect for you.
Yeah, I wish that was
the way life worked.
- [Shop Announcer] Sam, there's
a cleanup on aisle five.
Cleanup on aisle five.
- There's a cleanup
on aisle five.
- Hmm.
- I gotta go clean it up.
- That's you.
- That's me, yeah.
Hey, I'm sorry you're
feeling sad today.
(gentle music)
Bye.
- [Virginia] Hey, Sam?
- Yeah?
- Fuerte.
- For my next impressions,
I'm gonna impersonate Billy
Bob Thornton's character
from Sling Blade giving
Christopher Walken directions.
Take a right, then left, mm-hmm.
Then walk down,
hmm, take a right.
Don't understand
what you're saying.
You said take a right then
a left or left then a right?
I'm walking here and I'm
lost and I need help.
I need help, I need some help.
(Sam clears throat)
Oh, gosh.
- There's a guy in
the corner booth
who insists on
speaking with you.
Name's Desmond,
he's a talent scout.
- Huh.
Let's see what we got here.
- Sam.
The audience was crap tonight.
- Welcome to my life.
- Doesn't have to be like this.
I work for someone, an agent,
who can change
everything for you.
- Yeah.
What's the hook?
(Desmond laughs)
(tense music)
- Come on, Sam, there's no hook.
We think you have what it takes.
- All right, listen.
I already did the thing
where you pay the
agent to represent you
and I'm not gonna
fall for that again.
- No, no, no, no.
She's legit and she
wants what she wants.
And she wants you, Sam.
But it's a one-time offer.
(tense music)
There's the address.
She's expecting you tomorrow.
(tense music)
(footsteps receding)
- I gotta work tomorrow.
(tense music)
- [Van Sickle] Oh, Connie,
please report to Mr. Van
Sickle's office ASAP.
- Wow.
They're not even being
subtle about it anymore.
- Hey, was it true what
you said the other day?
- About you being good at
weaseling out of hard work?
- No, about me getting
better at my impersonations.
- I wouldn't lie
to you about that.
- All right, well here's one.
This is Owen Wilson
as an OB-GYN.
It's a girl, wow.
- Yeah, maybe work on that
one a little bit more.
- She's crazy as a
road lizard, wow.
- [Virginia] Oh gosh, Sam.
(urine sloshing)
- Surprise, surprise.
Look who ain't working.
Clean up, aisle nine.
Your mop awaits, Princess.
- [Store Announcer] Sam,
please report to the trash room
for box breakdown.
Sam.
(tense music)
(engine revving)
(door thuds)
(alarm beeps)
(birds calling)
- Hello, Mr. Reinhold.
We've been expecting you.
(gate creaks)
Follow me.
(footsteps clopping)
(tense music)
(footsteps approaching)
- Welcome, Sam.
I've been in this business
for a long time, Sam,
and I know talent when I
see it, and you have it.
- Thanks.
- Are you thirsty?
- Yeah, I'm a little thirsty.
Hmm, thanks.
(lively music)
- I never want you to be
thirsty, Sam, ever again.
You have greatness in you,
but no one sees it
and no one ever will,
unless someone
brings it out of you.
Do you currently have
representation, Sam?
- No.
No.
No, I'm on my own.
- Well, then it's simple,
let me represent you.
- It sounds great.
It also just sounds
too good to be true.
How do I know it's real?
- I thought you'd never ask.
(lively music)
Look.
See what I could give you.
(lively music)
(visions whooshing)
- How-
- I know where you've been.
Now it's up to you where you go.
All you've ever dreamt of,
Sam, really can be yours.
It's all right in front of you.
- Where do I sign?
(Madam laughs)
(Sam laughs)
- From now on, this
will be in your act.
Thank you, Sarah.
(tense music)
- A puppet?
You want me to
perform with a puppet?
By the way,
that is the creepiest little
puppet I've ever seen.
- Well, I think he's
kind of handsome.
Just like you, Sam.
(tense music)
From the Maori and Inuit to
the Zulu and ancient Greeks,
ventriloquism is
a sacred practice
that has been part of the
human experience for eons,
and it's power lives on.
- Then why are people with
puppets on kids TV programs?
- [Madam] Because like many
ancient rituals and beliefs,
ventriloquism slowly made
its way into the mainstream.
- Kinda like Hasbro
and Ouija boards.
- Take it or leave it.
This is the only way we work.
(tense music)
(voices whispering)
(Sam chuckles)
- Ah.
Where's the pen?
(Madam laughs)
- Oh dear, these sorts of
things aren't forged in ink.
(tense music)
Have a seat, Sam.
- This is cool.
Ow.
(tense music)
- [Madam] We're done here.
- Oh, what about the dummy?
- He'll be delivered soon.
Just one more thing.
(tense music)
(heart beating)
(camera flicks)
Welcome to the agency.
- Yeah.
- [Sarah] Follow me.
(Sam panting)
(water splashing)
(doorbell rings)
- [Grandpa] Sam?
(Grandpa coughs)
The door.
(birds chirping)
(dogs barking)
(phone rings)
- [Telemarketer] Mr. Reinhold-
- Stop calling here, please.
- [Telemarketer] Do
you have a moment-
(phone thuds)
(Grandpa coughing)
- What is this here?
(Sam laughs)
(tense music)
No one cared who I was
until I put on the mask.
(Sam laughs)
Nerd.
All right.
(eerie music)
Oh, son of a,
how the heck did you get
here, you freaky little thing?
So looks like we're gonna be
working together soon, huh?
Sam, it's nice to meet you.
Hi, Sam, it's nice to meet you.
Oh.
Hi, Grandpa.
- Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
What, there's two of you now?
(Sam laughs)
It's just a prop.
I'm gonna work it
into my new act.
And do you know why?
- [Grandpa] No.
- Because your grandson
got a new agent.
Yeah.
She gave me the prop
because she thinks it's
gonna help my career.
- Oh, Sam.
Sam, this is huge.
A new agent.
Oh, Sam, this is big
news, this is serious.
And what, she found
you at the club?
- Well, I mean, her
talent scout, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
Hey, guess what?
- [Grandpa] What?
- Something in the
mail just came for you
that is gonna make your
life a heck of a lot easier.
- Okay.
- All right, you ready?
- Yep.
- There we go.
- Okay, I am guessing this
is a new case of nymph flies
for our next fishing trip.
- I wish we could
afford a fishing trip.
But it is the next best thing.
You ready for this?
- [Grandpa] Yep.
- I want you to close your eyes.
- Okay.
- Keep them closed.
Ta-da.
- Hey.
- [Sam] Yeah, I took
your Medicaid check,
I got you a brand
new oxygen machine.
- Oh, whoopy.
- It's battery operated,
voice controlled,
it's light as a feather.
You don't have to walk around
with that tank of
oxygen anymore.
- You know, the
doctor was telling me
not to become
addicted to oxygen.
Too much O2 not good for you.
- You can't look a gift
horse in the mouth, Wilbert.
(Grandpa laughs)
- Don't gimme, Ed.
Don't gimme Ed.
Where's my tank?
- [Sam] It's right here.
Tell it, say, "Turn on machine."
- Turn on machine.
Oh no, I've entered
a whole new world.
(phone rings)
- [Sam] Hello.
You've reached the Reinholds,
you know what to do.
- [Telemarketer] Mr.
Reinhold, I'm sorry, Mr-
- Hey, I said stop calling here.
You've gotta stop calling.
This is basically harassment.
We are not interested.
Stop calling this number.
Golly.
(dial tone ringing)
(phone thudding)
What the?
(dial tone ringing)
You have like a little speaker
in your head or something?
A battery pack?
You're just a little dummy.
(tense music)
(reality trills)
(Sam imitates dial tone)
(Fergus imitates dial tone)
(Sam laughs)
(phone rings)
- Hey, you've called this number
243 times in the last year.
I know who you are.
I know that you are
wearing a red sweatshirt.
- [Telemarketer] Who is this?
- Call me Fergus, but you
better never call me again.
Bye.
(lively music)
(Sam laughs)
- Why Fergus, let's
see what else you got.
- Woo.
Well, I guess we can check
the old conveyor belt
off the list, huh?
- Yeah, I guess that means
we've pretty much
done it everywhere.
- Almost.
- Uh-huh.
- Oh.
- I have to pee.
- Yeah, you do.
- Mm.
(Van Sickle laughs)
At least you get
to look at that.
- Yeah.
Makes me want to go boom.
(phone ringing)
Yeah, Van Sickle,
manager of everything.
- [Fergus] I know you're
with that whore, Bobby.
- Karen, honey?
- After 20 years of marriage,
this is what you do?
I hope you get
gonorrhea and die.
- [Van Sickle] No.
(Sam laughs)
- Gonorrhea, Fergus?
(Fergus laughs)
- Ladies and gentlemen,
prepare to be amazed.
For the first time
ever here at Shims,
Sam and his little
friend, Fergus.
(audience applauds)
Okay.
To demonstrate the world-class
impressions of Sam Reinhold,
we're gonna have tonight's
audience pick one celebrity
and one cartoon character
for Sam to impersonate.
Now let's hear what you've got.
(audience chattering)
- [Audience Member]
James Earl Jones.
(audience chattering)
- Which celebrity would you
like to hear Sam impersonate?
- [Audience Member]
Jimmy Stewart.
- Now can I get a
cartoon character?
(audience chattering)
Something tells me you've got
a cartoon character in mind.
(audience member whispers)
Got it.
Okay, Sam.
Jimmy Stewart and Miss Piggy.
(audience applauds)
- Oh, okay.
All right.
- [Tony] Good luck.
- Let's see what I got.
Okay.
(audience applauding)
(tense music)
(reality trills)
♪ Buffalo girls can't
you come out tonight ♪
♪ Can't you come out tonight
♪ Buffalo girls can't
you come out tonight ♪
♪ And dance by the
light of the moon ♪
What'd you wish for when
you threw that rock?
- [Fergus] Well, if I tell
you it won't come true.
- What is it that
you want, Mary?
You want the moon?
Just say the word and I'll
throw a lasso around it
and I'll pull it down.
Say, that's a pretty good idea.
I'll get you the moon, Mary.
- I think I'd like that, Jimmy.
(audience laughs)
- I'm not Jimmy, I'm George.
- What?
No, you are not, you're Jimmy.
(audience laughs)
- Actually, Miss Piggy,
hold on a second,
we're in a major motion picture
and we're doing a scene here
and I'm playing a character.
I'm George Bailey
and you are Mary.
- I'm not Mary,
silly, I'm Miss Piggy.
- Okay, hold on a second.
Mr. Capra, Frank, we
gotta cut, we gotta cut.
The pig here, she's
ruining the scene.
- Pig?
(audience laughing)
I'll show you pig, Jimmy.
Moi's ruining the scene?
Here's what I think of that.
Hiiiya.
(upbeat music)
(audience applauds)
- Ladies and gentlemen,
Sam and Fergus.
Wow.
(audience applauding)
Whoa.
(upbeat music)
Look at that.
- Yeah.
That's crazy.
- Sam.
How long have you been working
on that Jimmy Stewart
impersonation?
- I don't know,
Tony, my whole life.
- That was incredible.
I've never seen anyone
slay a crowd like that,
especially one of our crowds.
If you keep
performing like that,
I'm gonna give you Friday night.
- Oh, you better not
be teasing me, Tony.
Hey, you won't regret it, Tony.
- Fergus.
- [Sam] Come here,
gonna hug you.
- [Tony] Ah.
- [Sam] I'm gonna hug you.
- [Tony] Get away from me.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you little
freaky little guy.
You've caught my
employer's attention, Sam.
Keep it up.
And every time you and
Fergus post on social media,
you'll be paid $5,000 a
story and 10 grand a post.
Now, I know, that's not much,
but not bad for a
day's work, right?
Thank you, man, that's a lot.
Yeah, that's,
thank you, Desmond.
(upbeat music)
All right, Fergus,
let's make $10,000.
You ready?
Say cheese.
- Cheese.
(upbeat music)
(tense music)
- [Fergus] Virginia.
Shouldn't you be on registers?
- Yeah, Connie, Van Sickle
already approved my break
so you don't need to,
I thought we're off until-
(Virginia gasps)
(Sam laughs)
- I got you.
- What the heck is that?
- My name is Sam Reinhold
and I run a family business.
And this is my son and my
business partner, Fergus.
- Okay, but how did you just
do Connie's voice like that?
- It's just no big deal, it's
something I'm working on.
I got a new prop, new act.
Virginia, meet Fergus.
Fergus, meet Virginia.
- Nice to meet you, Fergus.
- It's nice to
meet you, Virginia.
- Wow.
You look nice.
Different.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I feel a bit different.
- Now all you need is a haircut.
- Okay.
What have we got here?
What is this?
- Look at these.
Do you remember my
first team meeting?
They asked us to
do vision boards.
It's like three years ago.
- Yeah, I remember that.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hold on a minute.
So you've wanted to be
a biomedical engineer
since you started
working at the store?
- Mm-hmm.
- Wow.
- Six and a half semesters.
I don't have enough
time or money,
which means that I will
graduate in three years,
give or take.
- Wow.
- Hard work.
Proofs in the pudding.
- Did somebody say pudding?
- No, Sam.
(Sam laughs)
- All right, robotic
arm, I get that,
the organs, I understand,
you got the medical stuff.
The cross is obvious.
But this.
Why do you have a scale of
justice on your vision board?
- My dad, he was a lawyer.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm, and his dad,
lawmen all the way back.
- Huh, that's impressive.
- Mm-hmm.
- Something tells me
that he wasn't your
run-of-the-mill
ambulance chaser.
- No, no, far from it.
I mean, he cared about
truth and justice
and actual people
in the courtroom,
even when it wasn't so easy.
Then he died,
and mom offered to
pay for law school,
an offer I couldn't refuse.
But a year of contract
and civil procedure,
it just showed me that
practicing law was not me.
And she said,
"Virginia, you're destroying
the family legacy."
- Wow.
- And she cut me off.
- That's rough.
- That's her.
- Yikes.
- So here I am, Sam,
putting myself through school,
putting the super
in Super Duper-
- Did somebody say pudding?
- Stop it.
When I should be at the
library studying for midterms.
- Well, you want to
know what I know?
Your dad would be
very proud of you.
(gentle music)
You wanna know why I know that?
- [Virginia] Why?
- Because I am.
(gentle music)
- Well, look at these
two lovebirds, huh?
Virginia, your break's over,
and the two of you
both know the HR rules,
we don't fraternize with
coworkers now, do we?
Huh?
Okay, what in the Sam
Hill ugly freak thing,
what is that?
You bringing toys to work now?
- We're going.
- Till next time.
- Hey, are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Let's raise some hell.
(upbeat music)
Top of the day to ya.
This is your friendly
superstore manager,
Robert Van Sickle speaking.
And at Super Duper Superstore,
we honor our customers
and animals alike.
And here's a fun fact,
today is National
Chicken Day (clucks).
So in honor of today,
your favorite Super
Duper Superstore
is now offering right here and
now free rotisserie chicken
to any and all customers.
- Excuse me.
- [Sam] That's right,
free, free, free.
Come find me at
the chicken heater.
(upbeat music)
(customers chattering)
- Thank you.
- I'm the real manager.
Excuse me.
- [Customer] Free chicken.
- Sir, hey, these
are not free, okay?
They're not free.
Hey.
- [Customer] Here
for the free Chicken.
- [Customer] Hey,
don't touch my chicken.
(Sam and Fergus clucking)
Come find me at
the chicken heater.
- You gonna pay for that, ma'am?
- [Sam] I'll have
my toothpick in-
- Ma'am?
- And there's a V
on my belt buckle.
(upbeat music)
- What is going on?
Dear Vanny, I quit.
Sam.
Ha, you don't quit, I fire you.
(cone clutters)
(upbeat music)
- Hey, Kermit, back off.
I don't want you
steal my kingdom.
(upbeat music)
No, I'm not trying to
steal (indistinct).
Hey, it's not easy being me.
(upbeat music)
- Looking good, Sam.
You're looking good.
(crowd chattering)
- Ladies and gentlemen,
for weeks now,
Sam and Fergus have been
blowing our minds nightly.
What you are about to witness
has never been
attempted on stage.
But right here, right now,
I give you master
impressionist, Sam Reinhold.
(audience applauds)
But first, we need a volunteer.
Oh, we're sure not
lacking candidates.
You, the young lady in the blue.
Come on up here.
(audience applauds)
Yes.
And what's your name?
- Beth.
- Beth, thank you
so much for coming.
- Yeah, I love Sam and Fergus.
I've been to all
their performances,
I think their impressions
are unbelievable.
- Well, I know they
appreciate that.
- I love you, Sam.
- Well, let's put those
skills to the test.
What do you say?
You ready?
(audience applauds)
To prove that this is
unrehearsed and unrecorded,
I'm gonna ask the
audience for a prompt.
Once we decide on that prompt,
I want you to speak right
here into this microphone.
And then Sam-
- Hmm?
(audience laughs)
- I mean, Fergus will do
his best impression of you.
Got it?
- Got it.
- Okay, so the category for
tonight is children's songs.
(audience chattering)
Itsy-bitsy spider?
The itsy bitsy spider it is.
Okay, you ready?
♪ The itsy bitsy spider
went up the water spout ♪
♪ And down came the rain
and washed the spider out ♪
♪ Out came the sun and it
dried up all the rain ♪
♪ And the itsy bitsy spider
went up the spout again ♪
And that's how it's done.
(audience applauding)
Can I get a warm Shims
round of applause for that?
Thank you so much, Beth.
She even had the hand
motions and everything.
Now is the moment you've
all been waiting for.
Let's see if the world-famous
Sam Reinhold can,
with his head
literally underwater,
imitate Beth singing
the Itsy Bitsy Spider.
Drum roll, please.
(tables thudding)
(tense music)
(reality trills)
(water sloshing)
(suspenseful music)
(Fergus laughs)
♪ The itsy bitsy spider
went up the spout again ♪
♪ And that's what
it's all about ♪
(audience cheers)
(upbeat band music)
- How'd I do tonight?
- What do you mean?
You were right
there, they loved it.
The whole world is loving it.
You are blowing up, brother.
Check it out.
650,000 followers
practically overnight.
- Oh, my gosh.
- You know, Sam,
do you know 20 years ago I
was an intern for Jack Conrad?
- You were?
- And he's still a dear friend.
He told me that if I ever
came across a fresh talent
that he had to have on the
show, I can make a call.
I've never taken him up on
that offer until tonight.
Congratulations, Sam.
He wants you on the show.
- Are you kidding me?
- I kid but not about this.
This is serious.
- Jack Conrad?
Yeah, Tony.
Oh.
Oh, thank you.
- Well, at this rate,
you'll probably be poached
by those rumrunners over
at the Pioneer Center.
Gotta try to keep you
here somehow, right?
Great set.
- I love you, Tony.
I love you.
- Hey Sam.
- Hi.
- You really don't know
how much your
performances mean to me.
(Beth humming)
(patrons chattering)
- Well hello, Beth.
Oh, I missed.
(Sam gasps)
(Virginia laughs)
Hi.
- That was amazing.
- Hi.
- Amazing, Sam.
- You came.
- I wouldn't have
missed it for the world.
- Oh okay.
(patrons chattering)
(Sam whispering)
- Yeah.
Are you serious?
- I'm serious.
- Yes.
- That's amazing.
- Isn't that amazing?
- I'm so proud of you.
- The couple next door has
been going at it all morning,
and not in a good way.
- Grandpa.
Hat, sweater, I got
something to show you.
- Okay.
(bright music)
- Thank you.
"Sam.
Now you're the king
of your castle.
Soon you'll be
king of the world.
Madam."
(bright music)
Grandpa.
We're kings of the world.
- King of the world.
(Sam laughs)
(ducks quacking)
Ducks.
- Ducks.
- They've got ducks.
(bright music)
(keys jangling)
- Welcome home.
- Sammy, thank you.
Thank you.
I'm so proud of you.
- Do you wanna be
even more proud of me?
- Can I be?
- Guess who's going
to New York City?
- Uh-uh.
- Guess who's gonna be on The
Latest Show with Jack Conrad?
- No.
- Yes.
Dream coming true.
- The dream's coming true.
- Dream coming true.
- Hey, you hear that?
The dream is coming true.
- The dream is coming true.
(upbeat music)
- Any cool guest today, Dad?
- Well, the network insisted
we do another segment
on the goofy kid who
plays the bagpipes.
- Billy Murphy?
Dad, no.
Billy Murphy, babe.
He's so cringe, Dad.
- Oh, and what's his name?
The ventriloquist who's
blowing up right now?
- Sam Reinhold?
- [Jack] Mm-hmm.
- No way.
Babe, Sam Reinhold is
gonna be on the show.
Dad, he's goated.
- Yeah.
- Can I meet him?
- No.
You promised me you'd
pick up your sister.
A promise is a promise.
- But Zoe got to meet
Post Malone last week.
- We made a deal.
You can't just break the deal.
- Whatever.
- Somehow I think
you'll get through this.
I tell you what, watch
the show tonight,
and I promise I'll get him to
give you a special shout out.
- That sounds ass, effing sucks.
- Okay, don't talk to
me that way, Riley.
- Whatever.
(Jack sighs)
- Oh, thank you.
(upbeat music)
(audience cheering)
- [Producer] We're
going live in-
- And welcome back to the show.
Our next guest
has taken the entertainment
industry by storm,
and it is my immense pleasure
to welcome to the show master
ventriloquist, Sam Reinhold.
(upbeat music)
(audience applauding)
- Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
(upbeat music)
(audience applauding)
- All right, we're so
happy to have you on, Sam.
- Oh, thank you so much for
having me on, Mr. Conrad.
Literally, this is
a dream come true.
- Please call me Jack.
- (laughs) Okay.
Okay, Jack.
- Okay.
You know, Sam,
I have interviewed hundreds of
entertainers over the years.
Everyone from amateur yodelers
to professional
butter sculptors.
(audience laughs)
- Oh, that's quite a range.
- Yeah.
But you know, when it
comes to impersonations,
you really are one of a kind.
I can't do an impersonation
to save my life.
- I have a philosophy
about impersonation.
I feel like it is more
than just imitation.
When you really get it,
it is a person diving into
another person's soul,
capturing their spirit.
And if you're really good at it,
you can actually bring
somebody back to life
in the sacred space
of an audience,
if only even for a moment.
It really is a magical art.
(audience applauds)
Now, being funny, Mr. Conrad,
that's the hard part, no, no.
(audience laughs)
- Damn right, Sammy, damn right.
Being funny ain't
funny business.
- [Jack] He's right.
- I taught him everything
he knows, Jack.
- You know, you're only
the second ventriloquist
I've ever had on the show.
Why do you think that is?
- Frankly, because nobody
wants to work with the dummy.
- Exactly.
(audience laughs)
- Sorry, Fergus.
- The other ventriloquist was
the late great Dom Fletcher,
who had such a tragic
and untimely death
right when he was at
the top of his game.
- He really was a legend.
I mean, honestly, I wouldn't
be here if it weren't for him.
- What exactly does the dummy
bring to your performance?
- This might sound a little
corny, but we really are a team.
Fergus brings something
totally different to my show,
it's a totally
different dimension.
- And you are not worried at all
that he's gonna take
over the show, go solo,
and leave you in the dust.
(audience laughs)
(Sam laughs)
- Tell you what?
Jack, if he were to take
over my personal life,
I'd actually be pretty happy.
He could do the shopping,
the cooking, the cleaning.
He could do my
grandpa's laundry.
Ooh, can I say hi to my grandpa?
- Absolutely.
- Hey, grandpa.
Hi, Virginia.
We made it.
- Hey buddy boy, we made it.
(audience applauding)
- The dream has come true.
- You can do it, Sam.
- [Sam] The dream has come true.
- Yes.
- Okay well, we're
running out of time.
But before we go to commercial,
do you think we could
hear one quick impression?
- Oh, my gosh, I'd be honored.
- Hey, would you mind dedicating
it to my son, Riley Conrad?
He is a massive fan of yours.
- Of course.
All right, here we go.
Riley Conrad, this is for you.
(audience applauds)
(tense music)
- That sounds ass, effing sucks.
Do not talk to me
that way, Riley.
(tense music)
(audience applauds)
- Thank you, Sam and
Fergus for coming on.
- My pleasure.
- We'll be right back after
this commercial break.
(audience applauds)
- Thank you so much for-
- That was some trick
you just pulled.
- Uh, thank you.
- Something about you reminds
me so much of Dom Fletcher,
that it is scary.
I'm warning you.
Be careful, Sam.
'Cause if you don't have
your head on straight,
show business will be the
last business you are in.
(tense music)
(audience applauds)
- Never to be outdone,
tonight, Fergus will be
imitating audience members
while Sam eats a
pastrami sandwich.
- Yeah, but hang
on a second, Tony.
What am I, chopped liver?
- Well, you are
riding his coattails.
- Ayo.
Come on, don't give
this guy a big head,
he'll get too big for
his little britches.
I might have to replace him.
(audience laughs)
(tense music)
- Oh, you better watch it.
He might replace you.
(audience laughs)
Okay, tell me something
you did today.
- I got my dry cleaning done.
- Ready?
- Hey.
(audience applauds)
All right.
One of you tell me
something about your job.
- You-
- You go.
- You want to,
oh, I work in insurance.
- You, you go.
You want to, oh, I
work in insurance.
(audience applauds)
- Okay, what's your
pet's name, Ma'am?
- Spencer.
(tense music)
(Fergus grunting)
(hits thudding)
- Hey, let's take a short break
due to technical difficulty
and the Heimlich Maneuver.
(audience laughs)
(Sam panting)
- Hey, you ever pull a
stunt like that again
and I will throw
you in a blender.
(tense music)
(door thuds)
Sorry about that,
ladies and gentlemen.
Fergus got a little grumpy,
he's gonna take a nap.
But I'm gonna do
my impersonation
of Marlon Brando
getting an enema.
That feels nice, but
you forgot the bun.
Look, Tony, they
offered me a residency.
Conrad Show, where's
your loyalty, Sam?
- Hey, Tony, come on.
The Pioneer Center is the
Carnegie Hall of Reno.
And you know what they say.
It's show business.
- Yeah.
See you again on
the way down, Sam.
(patrons chattering)
(crickets chirping)
(alarm beeps)
(tense music)
- [Walter] Whoa, whoa.
- Don't touch me.
- I'm here to warn you.
- What are you talking about?
- Mem-Mec is the darkness,
the darkness breaks the light,
and they see everything.
Is he willing to die for it?
To die for it?
Are you willing to die for it?
- [Fergus] Oh Vanny.
- [Van Sickle] Connie?
- [Fergus] Vanny.
(Van Sickle laughs)
- Oh, Connie, baby.
(Fergus giggles)
- [Fergus] We're gonna
play a little game.
- Where are you at, you
naughty little girl, huh?
Connie.
(Fergus giggling)
- [Fergus] You're
getting warmer.
(lights zapping)
(broom clanks)
(eerie music)
- Connie?
(tense music)
All right, Connie, why don't
you just come out, okay?
It's just weird now.
(Ferguson giggles)
(eerie music)
What the?
(engine revving)
- Oh, what?
Wow.
Nice car.
How'd you get this?
- Well, let's just say that
business has been very good.
- I can see that.
- Would you like to
get in the car with me
and go for a ride?
I'd like to take you somewhere.
- Absolutely not.
Look what I'm wearing.
- Come on.
It's a surprise, I wanna
take you somewhere.
- No.
- [Sam] Why not?
- Give me 10 minutes.
- 10 minutes.
(gentle music)
- The Truckee River is
the only river in America
that flows north to east
and from lake to Lake.
- Okay.
- Lake Tahoe to Pyramid.
And in the early 1900s,
Reno used to be known as the
divorce capital of the world
because it took like six
weeks to get a divorce.
Newly exed wives would
stand on this bridge
and then would throw their
wedding rings into this river,
making it famous.
- Wow.
That's a lot of information
about the Truckee River.
Well done.
- It's a heck of a
lot of information
about the Truckee River, yes.
All right, your turn.
(water splashing)
- Mm.
Okay.
I have a story for you,
it's a ghost story.
- Ooh, I like a ghost story.
- And it started when I was 13.
I would fall asleep, I would
wake up, and I couldn't move.
- What do you mean?
- It's called sleep paralysis.
But with mine, there was
this entity in the room.
- Okay.
What kind of entity?
- Like a person standing
in the corner of the room.
- Okay, that's creepy, Virginia.
- Yeah, it was.
Over time, it did
get closer and closer
until he was sitting on my bed.
- Uh-oh, it's a he, so now
it's getting interesting.
- Forget it.
- No.
No, no, no, come on, come
on, come on, tell me.
I want to hear the story.
You got me, I'm hooked.
(suspenseful music)
(water sloshing)
- One night.
- [Sam] Yeah.
- I woke up paralyzed,
totally frozen,
and he'd gotten so close that
his hand was around my throat.
He was choking me.
I couldn't breathe, I couldn't
move, I couldn't scream,
I just saw myself
sinking into darkness.
And all I could only whisper
was one word, one thought,
a name.
(suspenseful music)
Jesus.
- Gosh, darn it, lady.
Then what happened?
- And the hand left my throat,
and then suddenly I could move.
And that's it.
It never happened again, ever.
- Hm.
Hm.
- You don't believe me.
- Yeah, I believe you.
- You don't think it's real.
- Hey, Virginia, I think
it absolutely is real,
I think it happened to you,
I just don't believe
in any of it.
I don't believe in God, I
don't believe in ghosts,
I don't believe in aliens.
Unless, you know, of course,
aliens are out there for us to
hunt and eat like space cow.
Hey Earl, this alien loin
is out of this world,
you gotta try it.
But other than that, no,
I think things are
exactly what they are.
I mean, that's it.
When it's done, it's done.
- That's it?
That's it, like over
is over for you?
- Wow.
We're going deep tonight, huh?
You wanna talk about death?
Yes, Virginia, I think
that when we die,
it's just nothingness,
it's worms and darkness.
It's all there is.
What?
What did I say?
- I don't know.
That night showed me something,
that no matter how insignificant
my life might feel,
I'm supposed to be here.
And that maybe there's something
beyond our miserable jobs
and our big dreams,
and maybe beyond
is where my dad is.
I would give anything, anything
to hear his voice again.
And yes, the thought that one
day I will, gives me hope.
- Virginia, I was just joking.
I wasn't,
what we have here is a
failure to communicate-
- [Virginia] Sam.
- Where are you going?
Where are you going?
- Not everything's a joke, okay?
This isn't a joke.
I just shared something
real with you,
and when you are ready to
share something real with me,
you know where to find me.
- Wait, where are you going?
(gentle music)
- Vanny.
Vanny?
This is not fun, Vanny.
This is so lame.
Wherever you are, we've
probably already done it there.
(Connie screams)
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- [Fergus] Hey, Gin Bug.
- Daddy?
- Ola, mija.
Do I love you this much?
No.
I love you this much.
- Who is this?
This is a sick joke.
Who is this?
(line beeps)
(tense music)
- They say every time
you eat a hot dog,
it takes 35 minutes
off your life.
I don't know who's in
charge of PR for hot dogs,
but they're not doing their job.
So here's a list
of American staples
and just how fast it's
trying to kill you.
Shake your hands
with the plumber,
23 minutes gone just like that.
I know.
Using a Q-tip, 12 minutes?
(audience laughs)
And that's the biggest
betrayal of them all because-
- Sam, before you go on,
I have to say that everyone here
at the Pioneer Center is happy
that you've finally chosen
to call this place your home.
- Yeah, it's my pleasure.
Thanks for having me, Clifton.
Oh, I have a question for
you logistically speaking.
How many days advance
notice do you need
if I wanna take some time off?
- You merely just
started performing
and you want time off?
- Yeah, I know, yeah.
How many days
notice do you need?
- Two weeks.
- So in two weeks,
I'm gonna take a week off to
take my granddad fly fishing.
It's a long overdue
trip and I want a rest.
- [Clifton] Stars,
you're all alike.
- It's a Q-tip conspiracy-
- [Audience Member]
Where's Fergus?
- [Audience Member] Yeah,
bring out Sam and Fergus.
- Well, the people have spoken.
I gotta get me a dummy
one of these days.
See you later.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
without further ado,
the king of ventriloquism,
Sam Reinhold, and Fergus.
(upbeat music)
(audience applauding)
- Whoa, whoa.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Ladies and gentlemen, Fergus.
(audience applauding)
- Hey.
Hi everybody.
- I just gotta say
before I start the show
my first night here
at the Pioneer Center,
this is honestly
a dream come true.
I've always wanted to
perform on this stage
ever since I was a little-
- Blah-blah-blah,
cut the crap, Sam.
- All right, Fergus.
(audience laughing)
- Hey, hello, nurse.
- Hey, be nice.
Hey, that's not how we
talk to our showgirls.
Showgirls, show
them what you do.
(upbeat music)
(audience applauding)
Ladies and gentlemen,
for the first time only
at the Pioneer Center,
bring out the pool.
- Hey ladies, time for
some skinny dipping.
Yes.
(audience laughs)
(upbeat music)
- Is anyone thirsty?
(audience applauding)
And now what I need you to do
is everybody to take a
look under your seats.
Go ahead, beneath your seats.
I need one red ticket.
Can you find it, people?
Can you find it?
The person who finds a ticket
wins a chance to come on stage
and participate in
Sam and Fergus' act
right here, right now.
Who has the ticket?
(audience chattering)
People, where's the ticket?
Who has the red ticket?
(tense music)
- Not gonna find it (laughs).
- Find the ticket.
Somebody has to have the
ticket, for God's sake.
There's a man on stage with
a tank of water on his head.
Who has the freaking ticket?
We gonna let him drown?
Find the ticket.
(Sam gurgling)
(glass shatters)
(audience gasps)
- So you want to go fishing
with grandpa, huh Sam?
You belong here
on stage with me.
I took care of Van
Sickle, wonder who's next.
- Best luck to Sam Reinhold,
but the show must go on.
So give us 10 minutes and we'll
bring Rob Plyman back out.
(tense music)
- Dumb.
Dumb.
It's not funny.
- Put your hands
together for Rob Plyman.
(tense music)
(audience applauding)
Rob Plyman.
(tense music)
(audience applauding)
Where are you at?
Rob?
(Rob laughs)
- Rob Plyman.
- [Clifton] Finally.
- Yeah.
- What's sure to be another
electrifying performance,
Rob Plyman, everyone.
- Hey, hey.
Give up for him, huh?
What a guy, whoa.
(audience applauding)
So I guess this
is what it's like
to be a proctologist in
Keebler factory, huh?
Huh?
Oh, you guys don't like cookies?
(tense music)
Well, this guy
looks familiar, huh?
- [Audience Member] You suck.
(audience member
speaks indistinctly)
- Hey, piss off.
(audience jeering)
(tense music)
- You know, you
do look like Sam.
Even the eyes are dead.
(Rob laughs)
(flesh squelching)
Hey.
Get it off me.
(audience members screaming)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Virginia] Hey,
Melvin, it's Virginia,
sorry for the late call.
- Oh, no, no, no, I was
up anyway waiting to see
if the Giants could get a hit.
What's up?
- [Virginia] It's Sam.
He wanted me to call you,
he's in the hospital.
- Hospital?
- He's all right.
Don't worry, he's okay.
They said chances are
he's gonna spend the night
at the hospital.
Are you okay on your own?
- [Grandpa] That's very
kind of you to ask.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
- Speaking of Sam, can
I ask you a question?
- [Grandpa] Yeah?
- He seems different.
Is he different to you?
- Well, Virginia, he's
very big-time now,
and that's a very big change
for some people to adjust to.
But I think just
hang tight, girl,
because the Sam that
you know and love,
he's gonna come back.
- Right.
I wanna believe that.
I'll check in with you tomorrow.
- Virginia, now
you sound worried.
Do you think Sammy's
gonna be okay?
- I hope so, but
I wanna make sure.
I need to check something out.
- You know, my daddy used to say
that a good woman could
see into the soul of a man.
He was right.
Thanks for the call.
- Goodnight, Melvin.
- [Grandpa] Increase
oxygen levels.
(tense music)
(dramatic music)
- Hi, do you still
have this book?
(dramatic music)
(bell dings)
Thank you.
(dramatic music)
(tense music)
(pages shuffling)
"To the ancient Greeks,
ventriloquism was
considered a means
by which the living
could talk to the dead.
Ventriloquism may serve as a
portal between both worlds.
When a portal is opened,
a beloved being or an
aggressive presence may pass
with the help of a guide who
has one foot in both worlds.
Lacking, in most cases,
a physical husk, the mimic,
a word derived from
Mesopotamian god Mem-Mec."
- I'm here to warn you.
Mem-Mec is the darkness, the
darkness drinks the light.
- "Will inhabit an object,
preferably one that
is frequently in
contact with its host."
"Controls it until death."
(Virginia gasps)
(tense music)
Sam.
- Sam.
Watch out.
Mem-Mec wants your-
(flesh squelches)
(engine revs)
(Grandpa wheezes)
- I'm not getting anything
out of this damn thing.
Increase oxygen levels.
(machine beeps)
(oxygen hisses)
Okay.
That's better.
Now we're talking.
Okay.
Now let's see if
we get a run here.
Oh, Sam?
- [Desmond] Hey, grandpa.
- Virginia called me.
Why didn't you call me?
- [Desmond] I just had the
strangest 24 hours of my life.
How'd you sleep?
- I didn't sleep,
I didn't sleep.
These heart meds
are just killing me.
Could you come down here and
take a look at this thing?
I mean, it's giving me trouble.
- [Desmond] Why don't you try
to get some sleep, Grandpa?
- Ah, wait.
(Grandpa wheezing)
Sam?
Sam where did you-
(Grandpa screams)
- [Desmond] Increase
oxygen level to 100%.
- [Grandpa] Yes, yes.
Thank you (indistinct).
(tense music)
(Grandpa gasping)
Sam.
(tense music)
(oxygen hissing)
(Grandpa gasping)
(tense music)
- [Desmond] Machine turn off.
(Grandpa gasping)
(tense music)
- Melvin Reinhold was
an exemplary soldier,
one who sacrificed himself both
on and off the battlefield.
The Talmud tells us, save one
life, save the entire world.
When Melvin saved the lives
of every man in his platoon
during the January 10 Offensive,
he saved entire worlds
for future generations
of all those families.
And Melvin loved his fly
fishing, largely, I believe,
for the memory-making
opportunities it afforded him
with his beloved grandson, Sam.
In this book,
we're taught that greater
love hath no man than this,
that a man lay down his
life for his friends.
Our friend Melvin was this man.
Sam.
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(gentle music)
- [Attendee] God bless you.
- Thank you, Sir.
(tense music)
Hey, you got some
balls showing up here.
- I am doing my job.
And it's in your best
interest for you to do yours.
- You know what?
I want out.
I want out, I'm done.
- You are bound
by your contract,
the same contract that
has lined your pockets
and placed you on
the world stage.
Your agent doesn't take
kindly to broken contracts.
(punch thuds)
(Sam groans)
(Virginia gasps)
(Sam gasping)
(tense music)
An invitation was delivered.
Our client needs you on
stage tonight performing,
or I'll show you how suffocating
show business can get.
(tense music)
(Sam clears throat)
(footsteps receding)
(tense music)
(Sam panting)
- You okay?
- [Sam] Yeah.
- Stop.
Are you okay?
- No.
(engine revving)
Every time I perform, I
don't know, I feel like,
it's like I lose a
little bit of myself.
- He's changing you.
- Yeah, but you don't
understand, Virginia,
I don't have a choice.
- You need to make
a choice, Sam.
What do you wanna do?
(tense music)
(heart beating)
- There's only one thing to do.
Fergus needs to retire.
(dramatic music)
(wood chipper chugging)
- Vaya con Dios, hombrecito.
- Break a leg, Fergus.
(dramatic music)
(wood chipper whirring)
Should we get outta Reno?
Let's just go away and hide out.
- No.
No hiding.
If they want you
to keep performing,
you should give
them a performance.
- How?
I just turned
Fergus into sawdust.
- I wish you could see
yourself the way I see you.
You're brilliant, Sam Reinhold.
You don't need Fergus,
you don't need anyone
to help you shine.
(gentle music)
- That's not true.
I need you.
(gentle music)
- [Tony] I couldn't be happier
to welcome back to Shims,
the one, the only, on the
stage where it all began,
Sam Reinhold.
- Get out there and crush it.
- Hey.
Fuerte.
(tense music)
(audience applauding)
- Well, well, well, if it
isn't my little friend, Fergus.
You know, Fergus, all work and
no play makes Sam a dull boy.
(audience laughs)
(tense music)
(reality trills)
- Oh, well.
(Fergus laughs)
(audience laughs)
Hi everybody.
I heard grandpa
was finally able to get
the rest that he needed.
That geezer sure is a
breath of fresh air.
Oh, Sam, I think we need
to catch these five
folks up, don't you?
Oh, what's the matter, Sam?
Does the cat got your tongue?
Anybody ever heard of the
Super Duper Superstore?
Well, it looks like it's
gonna need a cleanup
in the basement.
It's like a murder
scene down there.
- Get him off the stage now.
- No, I think it's
part of the act.
We got a little visitor.
Hi, Virginia.
Does everybody want to
hear me do an impersonation
of Virginia's dad?
Ola mija, do I
love you this much?
No.
I love you this much.
(audience gasps)
(body thuds)
- Sam, are you okay?
Are you okay?
- What happened?
- You have to end this.
(tense music)
(footsteps thudding)
- Hello?
Hello.
(voices chanting)
(tense music)
(voices whispering)
(door thuds)
- Please Sam, join us.
- [Sam] Desmond?
- Sam, my client has
enjoyed working with you,
and you are almost
ready for the big stage.
- Listen, I don't know
what kind of sick shit
that's going on here.
I don't want any part of it.
I don't want a part of
you anymore, I'm done.
- Not according
to your contract.
- Listen, lady, you
took everything from me.
I want my life back.
- It's funny you
should put it that way
because I gave you everything.
Your old life was pathetic.
Desmond, my book of names.
You know, Dom Fletcher had
a similar contract to yours,
then he refused to perform.
It didn't end well for Dom.
Now your contract,
Samuel M. Reinhold,
is also still in vigor.
So I suggest that you
continue to perform
for Mem-Mec through Fergus.
- No, never again.
(tense music)
- Well, there is one way
out of your contract.
It's simple.
In the contract that you
signed of your own free will,
you agreed that to break it,
you'd be willing to
give us what we want.
So if you want out,
it's time to make a
little sacrifice, Sam.
- You want me to
make a sacrifice?
You can go to hell.
(tense music)
(Sam grunting)
- These punks.
They think contracts were
made for breaking, don't they?
(Desmond laughs)
(voices chanting)
Oh, Sam, you break, you buy.
Sarah, bring me Fergus.
(dramatic music)
- Where the heck are you, Sam?
- Prepare the exchange.
(voices chanting)
(dramatic music)
Hurry, Sarah.
(tense music)
(voices talking indistinctly)
(blood patters)
- Sam?
(voices chanting)
Sam.
(tense music)
(taser zaps)
Sam?
- Don't stop.
- [Virginia] Are you okay?
- [Madam] Hello, puppet.
What is it you want?
- I wanna see Sam's
contract with your agency.
Show me 'cause I'm
sure whatever this is
depends on his consent,
which you don't have.
(tense music)
(blood sloshing)
Here, article three, section 16,
"If however the Signee can
provide a willing proxy
or stand-in for
their obligations
or if an independent party
of their own free will
fulfills the obligation
and the facilitation
of this contract for Signee,
said action shall render
this agreement null
and void for Signee."
I'll do it.
Whatever it is, I'll do it.
- How strange.
That hasn't happened
for centuries.
- Sam.
(gentle music)
I love you, Sam.
I've loved you from
the moment we met.
(gentle music)
I know you'd do the same for me.
(dramatic music)
(Virginia gasps)
(Virginia panting)
(tense music)
- [Desmond] We have our portion.
What we need is ours.
- Dump them on the beach.
Make it look like an overdose.
(tense music)
(Sam gasps)
- I'm so sorry.
No.
Hey.
(gentle music)
Virginia.
Forgive me.
(Virginia coughs)
(gentle music)
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Hey, it's all right.
(dramatic music)
- All of a sudden over
the last couple of weeks,
Sam Reinhold has gone
completely silent.
It's as if he
faked his own death
and just, poof, disappeared
from the face of the earth.
Well, wherever he
is, I miss the guy.
So in honor of Sam
Reinhold and Fergus,
everybody meet Eduardo.
(audience members laugh)
Thank you.
Eduardo, fun fact,
is from Austria,
and he only has a couple
sentences but it'll work.
Eduardo, how you
doing today, buddy?
(Will grunts)
(audience laughs)
Okay, that's one way
to answer a question.
That's fine, Eduardo.
Have you gone around the city?
Have you checked anything out?
Get to the chopper.
Oh, okay.
Thank y'all so much.
I'm Will Rhodes.
Thank you guys.
Yeah, thank you so much.
(patrons chattering)
- Hey Will, nice set.
- Hey Jerry.
- Look at this fancy
letter I just got.
It's addressed to you.
And if it's what I think it is,
your ship has finally arrived.
These gray skies
are gonna clear up,
so put on a happy face.
- Thanks Jerry.
- Hey, Andy.
(footsteps receding)
- Okay.
(tense music)
(patrons chattering)
(lively music)
(dramatic music)